



VICTOR REVERTER



Madrid, Spain



victormanuel.cuba@gmail.com



Victor Reverter



victorreverter.com



Top Skills

Photoshop IMTH Illustrator CSS & Preprocessors After Effects Javascript & ES6 Premiere React InDesign Git & Github Figma Browser Dev Tools Responsive Design Sketch Web Performance Affinity Designer Affinity Photo Testing Affinity Publisher Debugging



Expertise

Protyping Team Work
Wireframing Agile Methods
Creativity Communication
Coding Time Management
Problem Solving Public Speaking



Languages

Spanish • English

French



About me

I'm is Victor Reverter a Senior Graphic, UX & UI Designer and Frontend Dev based in Madrid, Spain. Through my life and experiences working on creative process I think that some key points in everything we do are the passion, keep sharpening skills and always set upper goals.

Because of those beliefs I am a person who loves never stop learning, tell stories, show data, create great experiences through products and always trying to look for the right approach in every case.



Career

Graphic and Web Designer at Premdan - April 2015 to September 2015

The sector of the company was the translation. I had here my first professional job as college internship. Where I made different graphic and web design projects which helped to the company with theirs business.

Creative Designer at Telecoming - October 2015 to March 2016

My work in my second internship was primarily doing graphic design projects, but at the end I finished doing web design projects as well.

Web Designer at Telecoming - April 2016 to June 2019

After my internship I remained in the same company, but then I did both graphic and web design projects and now some projects that included User Interfaces (UI).

Senior Web Designer at Telecoming - July 2019 to Present

After more than three years the company considering my experience has given me the new role as "Senior".

Now I can even more be a support for new workmates or members of the company who require my experience and knowledge. I keep doing both kind of Projects graphic, web design and some UI.



Education

Design Degree at University Complutense de Madrid (UCM) -September 2011 to June 2015

Four years learning the base of design in many professional fields like 3D Sculpture, Animation, Scenography, Graphic Design, Web Design, Photography, etc.

Full Stack Web Development Certification at Free Code Camp - July 2015 to January 2017

I learnt more with this course about programming and web development of Frontend products.

LinkedIn Certifications - December 2018 to December 2019

For a year I got a LikedIn Premium Subscription for keep updated and learn new skills. So then there I learned new skills like React programming, ES6, UX & UI, Javascript, etc.

I have some of the courses certificates that I have taken published right directly on my LinkedIn profile where everyone can see it.

Multiple Sources - May 2020 to Present

As I like to keep updated in the last months I have been learning new skills on multiple platforms like Pluralsight & Platzi, among others. With the main goal of never stop learning and trying to be better.